[{"question":" How does a matrix differ from a data frame?","options":[{"text":"A matrix may contain numeric values only.","correct":true},{"text":"A matrix must not be singular.","correct":false},{"text":"A data frame may contain variables that have different modes.","correct":false},{"text":"A data frame may contain variables of different lengths.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What value does this statement return?","options":[{"text":"1","correct":false},{"text":"365","correct":true},{"text":"4","correct":false},{"text":"12","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What do you use to take an object such as a data frame out of the workspace?","options":[{"text":"remove()","correct":true},{"text":"erase()","correct":false},{"text":"detach()","correct":false},{"text":"delete()","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Review the following code. What is the result of line 3?","options":[{"text":"[1] 1 2 3","correct":false},{"text":"[1] \"1\" 2 \"3\"","correct":false},{"text":"[1] \"1\" \"2\" \"3\"","correct":true},{"text":"[1] 7 9","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nxvect<-c(1,2,3)\nxvect[2] <- \"2\"\nxvect\n```"},{"question":" The variable height is a numeric vector in the code below. Which statement returns the value 35?","options":[{"text":"`height(length(height))`","correct":false},{"text":"`height[length(height)]`","correct":true},{"text":"`height[length[height]]`","correct":false},{"text":"`height(5)`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" In the image below, the data frame is named rates. The statement `sd(rates[, 2])` returns 39. As what does R regard Ellen's product ratings?","options":[{"text":"sample with replacement","correct":false},{"text":"population","correct":false},{"text":"trimmed sample","correct":false},{"text":"sample <-- not sure","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which choice does R regard as an acceptable name for a variable?","options":[{"text":"`Var_A!`","correct":false},{"text":"`\\_VarA`","correct":false},{"text":"`.2Var_A`","correct":false},{"text":"`Var2_A`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the principal difference between an array and a matrix?","options":[{"text":"A matrix has two dimensions, while an array can have three or more dimensions.","correct":true},{"text":"An array is a subtype of the data frame, while a matrix is a separate type entirely.","correct":false},{"text":"A matrix can have columns of different lengths, but an array's columns must all be the same length.","correct":false},{"text":"A matrix may contain numeric values only, while an array can mix different types of values.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which is not a property of lists and vectors?","options":[{"text":"type","correct":false},{"text":"length","correct":false},{"text":"attributes","correct":false},{"text":"scalar","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the image below, the data frame on lines 1 through 4 is names StDf. State and Capital are both factors. Which statement returns the results shown on lines 6 and 7?","options":[{"text":"StDf[1:2,-3]","correct":false},{"text":"StDf[1:2,1]","correct":true},{"text":"StDf[1:2,]","correct":false},{"text":"StDf[1,2,]","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which function displays the first five rows of the data frame named pizza?","options":[{"text":"BOF(pizza, 5)","correct":false},{"text":"first(pizza, 5)","correct":false},{"text":"top(pizza, 5)","correct":false},{"text":"head(pizza, 5)","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You accidentally display a large data frame on the R console, losing all the statements you entered during the current session. What is the best way to get the prior 25 statements back?","options":[{"text":"console(-25)","correct":false},{"text":"console(reverse=TRUE)","correct":false},{"text":"history()","correct":false},{"text":"history(max.show = 25)","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". d.pizza is a data frame. It's column named temperature contains only numbers. If u extract temperature using the [] accessors, its class defaults to numeric. How can you access temperature so that it retains the class of data.frame?","options":[{"text":"`class( d.pizza( , \"temperature\" ) )`","correct":false},{"text":"`class( d.pizza[ , \"temperature\" ] )`","correct":false},{"text":"`class( d.pizza$temperature )`","correct":false},{"text":"`class( d.pizza[ , \"temperature\", drop=F ] )`","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```\n> class( d.pizza[ , \"temperature\" ] )\n> \"numeric\"\n```"},{"question":". What does c contain?","options":[{"text":"[1] NaN","correct":false},{"text":"[1] -4","correct":false},{"text":"[1] 4 -1 -1 2","correct":false},{"text":"[1] TRUE FALSE FALSE TRUE","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```\na <- c(3,3,6.5,8)\nb <- c(7,2,5.5,10)\nc <- a < b\n```"},{"question":". Review the statements below. Does the use of the dim function change the class of y, and if so what is y's new class?","options":[{"text":"No, y's new class is \"array\".","correct":false},{"text":"Yes, y's new class is \"matrix\".","correct":true},{"text":"No, y's new class is \"vector\".","correct":false},{"text":"Yes, y's new class is \"integer\".","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\n> y <- 1:9\n> dim(y) <- c(3,3)\n```"},{"question":". What is `mydf$y` in this code?","options":[{"text":"list","correct":false},{"text":"string","correct":false},{"text":"factor","correct":false},{"text":"character vector","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How does a vector differ from a list?","options":[{"text":"Vectors are used only for numeric data, while list are useful for both numeric and string data.","correct":false},{"text":"Vectors and lists are the same thing and can be used interchangeably.","correct":false},{"text":"A vector contains items of a single data type, while a list can contain items of different data types.","correct":true},{"text":"Vectors are like arrays, while lists are like data frames.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What statement shows the objects on your workspace?","options":[{"text":"list.objects()","correct":false},{"text":"print.objects()","correct":false},{"text":"getws()","correct":false},{"text":"ls()","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What function joins two or more column vectors to form a data frame?","options":[{"text":"rbind()","correct":false},{"text":"cbind()","correct":true},{"text":"bind()","correct":false},{"text":"coerce()","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Review line 1 below. What does the statement in line 2 return?","options":[{"text":"[1] 1 2 4 5","correct":false},{"text":"\"C\"","correct":false},{"text":"[1] \"1\" \"2\" \"C\" \"4\" \"5\"","correct":true},{"text":"[1] 1 2 C 4 5","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\n1 mylist <- list(1,2,\"C\",4,5)\n2 unlist(mylist)\n```"},{"question":". What is the value of y in this code?","options":[{"text":"Inf","correct":false},{"text":"Null","correct":false},{"text":"NaN","correct":false},{"text":"NA","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```\nx <- NA\ny <- x/1\n```"},{"question":". Two variable in the mydata data frame are named Var1 and Var2. How do you tell a bivariate function, such as cor.test, which two variables you want to analyze?","options":[{"text":"`cor.test(Var1 ~ Var2)`","correct":false},{"text":"`cor.test(mydata$(Var1,Var2))`","correct":false},{"text":"`cor.test(mydata$Var1,mydata$Var2)`","correct":true},{"text":"`cor.test(Var1,Var2, mydata)`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A data frame named d.pizza is part of the DescTools package. A statement is missing from the following R code and an error is therefore likely to occur. Which statement is missing?","options":[{"text":"`attach(d.pizza)`","correct":true},{"text":"`summarize(deliver)`","correct":false},{"text":"`mean <- rbind(d.pizza,count)`","correct":false},{"text":"`deliver[!complete.cases(deliver),]`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nlibrary(DescTools)\ndeliver <- aggregate(count,by=list(area,driver), FUN=mean)\nprint(deliver)\n```"},{"question":". How to name rows and columns in DataFrames and Matrices F in R?","options":[{"text":"data frame: names() and rownames() matrix: colnames() and row.names()","correct":false},{"text":"data frame: names() and row.names() matrix: dimnames() (not sure)","correct":true},{"text":"data frame: colnames() and row.names() matrix: names() and rownames()","correct":false},{"text":"data frame: colnames() and rownames() matrix: names() and row.names()","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which set of two statements-followed by the cbind() function-results in a data frame named vbound?","options":[{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nv1<-c(1,2,3)\nv2<-c(4,5,6))\nvbound<-cbind(v1,v2)\n```"},{"question":". ournames is a character vector. What values does the statement below return to Cpeople?","options":[{"text":"records where the first character is a C","correct":false},{"text":"any record with a value containing a C","correct":false},{"text":"TRUE or FALSE, depending on whether any character in ournames is C","correct":false},{"text":"TRUE or FALSE values, depending on whether the first character in an ournames record is C","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the value of names(v[4])?","options":[{"text":"\"\"","correct":true},{"text":"d","correct":false},{"text":"NULL","correct":false},{"text":"NA","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nv <- 1:3\nnames(v) <- c(\"a\", \"b\", \"c\")\nv[4] <- 4\n```"},{"question":". Which of the following statements doesn't yield the code output below. Review the following code. What is the result of line 3?","options":[{"text":"x[c(2, 3, 4)]","correct":false},{"text":"x[-1]","correct":false},{"text":"x[c(-1, 0, 0, 0)]","correct":false},{"text":"x[c(-1, 2, 3, 4)]","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```\nx <- c(1, 2, 3, 4)\nOutput: [1] 2 3 4\n```"},{"question":". Given DFMerged <- merge(DF1, DF2) and the image below, how manu rows are in DFMerged?","options":[{"text":"6","correct":false},{"text":"9","correct":false},{"text":"3","correct":false},{"text":"0","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```\nDF1(data frame 1): DF2(data frame 2):\nVarA VarB VarA VarD\n1 1 2 1 18 21\n2 4 5 2 19 22\n3 7 8 3 20 23\n```"}]